<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<patches>
    <patch>
    <name>22023-07-19 XCC - XCC and SIP gateway restart behavior fix2 xphone</name>
    <version></version>
    <description>DE Dieser Patch - behebt das Problem (Alcatel OXE in combination with the AnyNode), dass die Anrufernummer nicht aktualisiert wurde, wenn der Team Desk Anrufer von einem PBX Telefon in die Team Desk Grupper vermittelt wurde. - beschleunigt das Neustartverhalten der XCC und SIP Gw PBX Objekte EN This patch - fixes the problem (Alcatel OXE in combination with the AnyNode) that the caller number was not updated when the Team Desk caller was transferred from a PBX phone to the Team Desk group. - accelerates the restart behaviour of the XCC and SIP Gw PBX objects.</description>
    <downloadlink>https://github.com/C4BCSMORG/Patches/raw/main/V9.0.229/2023-07-19_XCC_-_XCC_and_SIP_gateway_restart_behavior_fix2_xphone_9.0.229.exe</downloadlink>
  </patch>
  <patch>
    <name>2023-08-08 Mail2Fax versteht lange ISO Filenamen xphone</name>
    <version></version>
    <description>DE Mail2Fax kann jetzt mit Filenamen im SMTP Header umgehen, die folgendes Format haben: name*0*=utf-8''HM_%C3%84nderung001.pdf filename*0*=utf-8''HM_%C3%84nderung001.pdf; EN Mail2Fax can now handle filenames in the SMTP header that have the following format: name*0*=utf-8''HM_%C3%84nderung001.pdf filename*0*=utf-8''HM_%C3%84nderung001.pdf;</description>
    <downloadlink>https://github.com/C4BCSMORG/Patches/raw/main/V9.0.229/2023-08-08_Mail2Fax_versteht_lange_ISO_Filenamen_xphone_9.0.229.exe</downloadlink>
  </patch>
  <patch>
    <name>2023-08-17 UMSServices handle leak fix xphone</name>
    <version></version>
    <description>DE Fixt ein leak von thread und event handles in IVFax2Print und IVSMTPReceiver das durch den UMSCOMClient verursacht wird. EN Fixes a leak of trhead handles in IVFax2Print and IVSMTPReceiver caused by UMSCOMClient.</description>
    <downloadlink>https://github.com/C4BCSMORG/Patches/raw/main/V9.0.229/2023-08-17_UMSServices_handle_leak_fix_xphone_9.0.229.exe</downloadlink>
  </patch>
  <patch>
    <name>2023-09-08 Softphone - consultation transfer fix xphone 9.0.229</name>
    <version></version>
    <description>DE Dieser Patch behebt das Problem, dass bei einer Rückfrage wärend dem Rufaufbau zum zweiten Partner ein Transfer möglich war, was zu mehreren folge Problemen geführt hat. EN This patch fixes the problem that a transfer was possible during a consultation call to the second partner, which led to several subsequent problems.</description>
    <downloadlink>https://github.com/C4BCSMORG/Patches/raw/main/V9.0.229/2023-09-08_Softphone_-_consultation_transfer_fix_xphone_9.0.229.exe</downloadlink>
  </patch>
</patches>